ICI Prudential Insurance Company
Limited has various number of employees in the
state number one and four post. Candidates having TSLC or Plus
Two passed in Agriculture, Animal and Botany subject should apply by email. Agritech IGI Pril Kam email address. Candidates having TSLC or
Plus Two passed in Agriculture, Animal and Botany subject should
prefer to apply by email.
When notification is received, please
subscribe bell icon to get notification.
IGI Pril Insurance
Company Limited is looking for Agricultural and Animal Technological
posts in the following areas. Technical
person should have complete details about the qualifications mentioned in this notification. This information technical post should be published within
15 days. The company should send the
application by email to Agritech IGI Pril Kam email address. I am
inviting applicants for the post of
Agricultural and Animal Technological candidate having qualifications mentioned in this notification.
Candidates who have passed SLC or So Sir examination in Agriculture or Animal Science or Botany and should have one year training in Agriculture or Animal Science subject or have passed Plus Two class in Agriculture or Animal Science subject and the
places to be given priority are Okhaldhunga for State No. 1,
Sol Khub Ma Mango for State No. 2,
Dhanusa Mahtari Bara Siraha for
State No. 2, Nuwakot for State No. 3,
Dharni Mango for State No. 4,
Gorkha.  In Lamjung, State, No., Palag Na,
District, West, Experienced and permanent candidate of insurance company is
given priority. Present some documents along with request,
filled in documents, documents which should be clearly visible,
applicant should bring copy of educational certificate along with bio-data,
copy of
citizenship statement card, copy of
education and experience letter, and passport size
photo, if you want to work in which company.  If you can
present any work experience under the status then give more priority.
If you want to work in any insurance company
or want to work in insurance company area then if you have any
experience then
status card card PIN card sorry if you have
ID card or work experience document
certificate then you can present it. The
priority candidate is only the person who has not come to the center, then the
process has increased, all the
systems are giving information to the company, IGI, Prerence,
notification chain, all the things,
now
Namaskar Jai Nepal.  Radhe Radhe